1tube.my 2012-05-03

# 1tube Dot My | About Us

**Privacy Policy**  
The use of this version of the "1tube.my" website and/or 1tube.my software and any other related software, upgrades or updates and all related services and special offers provided by "1tube.my" are subject to the hereunder provisions of this Privacy Policy.:

**General**  
"1tube.my" takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information, which we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information.  
BY USING OR ACCESSING ANY 1tube.my WEBSITE OR DOWNLOADING AND USING THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. 1tube.my MAY AMEND THIS POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME.  
If you are under the age of 13, you are not eligible to use the Service, and we ask you not to submit any personal information to us. We need parent approval, hence parent's account.

**Collection of Information**  
**Personal Information:** Use of certain features of the Service may require submission of certain personal information, including your first and last name, email address, a nick name (or other user ID) and a password.  
**Non personally identifiable Information:** 1tube.my may also collect or receive additional non personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the 1tube.my Service or website(s), and responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on 1tube.my's Service and/or website(s).  
"1tube.my" may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non personally identifiable technical information, when the 1tube.my website(s) and pages are visited or when the 1tube.my Service is used.

**How is the information being used?** The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by 1tube.my, to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you ; to fulfill your requests for Services, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of the Service and/or website(s), offerings and advertisements presented on 1tube.my Service, email communication, website(s) and pages; and to help offer you other Services, programs, or services that may be of interest.  
_Any personally identifiable information of yours_ will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. 1tube.my may use this information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about various groups of 1tube.my users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you.  
_Notwithstanding the foregoing_ , your information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures.

**Cookies:** "1tube.my" may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Service and/or of 1tube.my's website, including to operate and improve offerings through the Service and/or website; to help authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Service, and/or website; to remember your preferences and registration information; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the various offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon); and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you.  
Additionally, "1tube.my" or its advertisers may use other companies, known as third party ad servers to help present advertisements online in connection with the Service, and/or web sites. These third party ad servers may use cookies or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies, not 1tube.my's.  
"1tube.my" does not require that you accept cookies, and you may disable cookies at any time. However, some functionality of our Services and/or web sites may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies.

**Special Note for Parents**  
"1tube.my"'s Service and website are not intended for a general audience, and children under the age of thirteen (13) are not permitted to register with 1tube.my's Service and websites.

**Modification and Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information (Opt-Out)**  
In order to delete the personally identifiable information you submitted, notify us, to the following email address: admin@1tube.my that you wish to delete your personally identifiable information or any part thereof contained at our databases.

**Modification**  
If you wish to modify or update your personally identifiable information, use the web-site or application interface. If you need help, please contact us at the following email address: admin@1tube.my. Please note that deletion of your personally identifiable information from 1tube.my's database will not prevent 1tube.my from using gathered anonymous information.

**Third Parties' Practices**  
This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices exercised by other provides of products or services, advertisers or other web sites, or companies/people that 1tube.my does not own or control, or does not employ or manage.

|   | 

Contact Us   
admin@1tube.my
